<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<document-metadata version="1.0" xmlns="http://breeze.macromedia.com/">
	<document-info>
		<title>SnapEnwrap</title>
		<summary></summary>
		<author/>
		<keywords/>
		<thumbnail href="data/thumb/thumb_slide_000001.jpg"/><view-link href="/Viewer.swf?slide={position}"/>
	</document-info>
	<section type="slide" position="1" xmlns="">
		<title>Snap/enwrap System </title>
		<content>Snap/enwrap System Talus Basics Training </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
		<thumbnail href="data/thumb/thumb_slide_000001.jpg"/></section>
	<section type="slide" position="2" xmlns="">
		<title>Agenda </title>
		<content>Magma Confidential - 2 Snap/enwrap Agenda What is the snap/enwrap system? Terminology Flow chart Key commands Modifying fix… commands Other built-in procedures  </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
		<thumbnail href="data/thumb/thumb_slide_000002.jpg"/></section>
	<section type="slide" position="3" xmlns="">
		<title>What Is Snap/enwrap? </title>
		<content>Magma Confidential - 3 Snap/enwrap What Is Snap/enwrap? The snap system is most useful for: Controlling and modifying the design flow Automating methodology Ensuring that tasks such as reports and database saves are done at fixed points in the flow The snap system provides: Flow reporting – Easy interface generates all reports needed to access flow and design metrics Flow capture and summary – Summarizes all commands executed during the flow, with memory usage and runtimes Flow control – Automatically skips previously executed steps Enable all of these features by using the enwrap command </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
		<thumbnail href="data/thumb/thumb_slide_000003.jpg"/></section>
	<section type="slide" position="4" xmlns="">
		<title>What Good Is It? </title>
		<content>Magma Confidential - 4 Snap/enwrap What Good Is It? A script with everything enwrapped is easy to use and reuse If you import a Volcano that was exported halfway through the flow and source the same script, everything that was already executed gets skipped automatically There is no need to edit the script For this reason, all default fix… commands are fully enwrapped scripts  You can generate a complete flow summary based on this data with report snap flow You can use the report to verify which commands were executed during a flow, and analyzes the impact of flow changes on runtime </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
		<thumbnail href="data/thumb/thumb_slide_000004.jpg"/></section>
	<section type="slide" position="5" xmlns="">
		<title>Terminology </title>
		<content>Magma Confidential - 5 Snap/enwrap Terminology Location  An attribute that labels a point in the flow If it does not exist, it is created and set “true” by an enwrap command If it exists and is “false”, it is set “true” by an enwrap command If it does exist and is “true”, enwrap does not change the attribute Procedure A list of commands associated with a location and a level Most procedures generate reports or export Volcano databases Level A parameter that controls the execution of a list of procedures The default level produces fewer reports than the high level </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
		<thumbnail href="data/thumb/thumb_slide_000005.jpg"/></section>
	<section type="slide" position="6" xmlns="">
		<title>What Does enwrap Do? </title>
		<content>Magma Confidential - 6 Snap/enwrap What Does enwrap Do? Location attribute? do Command set Location find Level do Procedure for Level and Location F T Message/Warning enwrap {command} location model config snap level level config snap procedure procedure config snap output on  \      level procedure location A procedure must be defined before execution by enwrap, so config… statements must precede enwrap statement in your script. “Enwrapped” command </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
		<thumbnail href="data/thumb/thumb_slide_000006.jpg"/></section>
	<section type="slide" position="7" xmlns="">
		<title>Relationships of Key Commands </title>
		<content>Magma Confidential - 7 Snap/enwrap Relationships of Key Commands enwrap: Executes the enwrapped command and generates snap output for that location The “location” is stored as an attribute By default, enwrap skips the command if “location” is true config snap procedure: Defines snap output generated by enwrap Most procedures create reports, Volcano databases, and other output files config snap output: Associates snap locations with a snap procedure and level, and directs enwrap when to generate what output query snap output and report snap output: Reports all associated snap locations and procedures </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
		<thumbnail href="data/thumb/thumb_slide_000007.jpg"/></section>
	<section type="slide" position="8" xmlns="">
		<title>How to Modify fix… commands </title>
		<content>Magma Confidential - 8 Snap/enwrap How to Modify fix… commands Anything you can do in Blast to modify fix… scripts, you can do in Talus You do it a different way, using the snap system You need to know the enwrap location Find it from MOLTEN or your A.E. config snap replace level location command Changes enwrapped commands before they execute Remove commands with -erase or change them to “puts” config snap procedure and config snap output Add new commands at a given location Note: The only variable passed to the procedure by the enwrap command is $m. Declare any other variables as global variables inside the  config snap procedure command. config snap procedure "fault_cover" {global l run dft scan fault_coverage $m $l} </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
		<thumbnail href="data/thumb/thumb_slide_000008.jpg"/></section>
	<section type="slide" position="9" xmlns="">
		<title>One Way to Add to fix… commands </title>
		<content>Magma Confidential - 9 Snap/enwrap One Way to Add to fix… commands These two config… commands add additional commands the first time an enwrap command with the location  fix-netlist-final is run In this example, the procedure is to generate a hierarchical area report, but it could be any Talus or Tcl command config snap  procedure "hierarea" {  report area $m -hier -file $outputPrefix${sep}area_hier.rpt } config snap output on default hierarea fix-netlist-final    Procedure  name Location (from enwrap command in fix netlist) Level </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
		<thumbnail href="data/thumb/thumb_slide_000009.jpg"/></section>
	<section type="slide" position="10" xmlns="">
		<title>Another Way to Add to fix… commands </title>
		<content>Magma Confidential - 10 Snap/enwrap Another Way to Add to fix… commands preSourceTcl / postSourceTcl – At every location, the snap system searches for a file in the run directory called location.before.tcl or location.after.tcl, respectively.  If the file exists, the tool sources it. You can create these files while the fix… command is running without halting execution  </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
		<thumbnail href="data/thumb/thumb_slide_000010.jpg"/></section>
	<section type="slide" position="11" xmlns="">
		<title>Other Built-in Snap Procedures </title>
		<content>Magma Confidential - 11 Snap/enwrap Other Built-in Snap Procedures workVolcano - Unlike the default Volcano snap procedure, this command exports a Volcano database with only design data (i.e. no libraries).  Useful to save disk space and decrease runtime. emailMe – Sends an email to the address from config snap email_address pageMe – Sends a short email to the address from config snap pager_address </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
		<thumbnail href="data/thumb/thumb_slide_000011.jpg"/></section>
	<section type="slide" position="12" xmlns="">
		<title>Summary </title>
		<content>Magma Confidential - 12 Snap/enwrap Summary What is the snap/enwrap system? Terminology Flow chart Key commands Modifying fix… commands Other built-in procedures  </content>
		<related-content></related-content>
		<thumbnail href="data/thumb/thumb_slide_000012.jpg"/></section>
</document-metadata>
